http://www.royalneighbors.org/privacy

Products
Whether you’re just starting a family or heading toward retirement, life is full of ups and downs and the unexpected.
Annuities
Whether you’re just starting a family or heading toward retirement, life is full of ups and downs and the unexpected.
Privacy
Royal Neighbors Privacy Notice[ Web, PDF ]Opt-Out Form[ PDF ]For California Residents - CCPA Forms
Request for Information[ PDF ]Request to Correct Information[ PDF ]
Website PrivacyOur Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in the footer of every page of the site. The Information We Collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Royal Neighbors of America web site. On some pages, you can make requests or complete transactions. The types of personal information collected at these pages include: NameAddressEmail addressIncome and other demographic informationHow We Use InformationWe use the personal information you provide about yourself when completing a transaction or process to complete that transaction or process. We may also collect information from you when you agree to voluntarily respond to our request for additional information. We do not share this information with outside parties except as is needed to store the information provided or is otherwise permitted by law.We use return email addresses to answer the emails we receive. Such addresses may be used to communicate with you about upcoming Royal Neighbors activities or upcoming elections of our Board of Directors. We will only use email addresses sent to us using our Contact Us form and online chat in order to respond. We also provide you with opportunities to opt into receiving additional information from us. You may be able to register with our web site if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Any other information you submit on our web site will not be used for this purpose unless you indicate that you want to be added to our mailing list. You may also unsubscribe at any time from receiving future email offers from us.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site and to better tailor our services and products to your interests. Non-identifying information means that your name or ID is not directly associated with your use of the site.  Aggregate information means that your anonymous use of the site along with that of other site visitors are collectively used to determine which areas of the site are being used often and which are not. (Aggregate information also includes your anonymous responses to site surveys combined with the responses of other site visitors.  We use services such as Google Analytics to better understand your experience on our web site. We will only provide to Google an aggregation of all of the various users’ experience on our site which will not identify your usage on the site even if you have obtained other services from Google. If you wish to not have Google track your usage of our site you will need to go to the Google site and request to have your activities no longer tracked.We use information collected from cookies email addresses and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. We will provide tailored content based on your prior usage and other information you have voluntarily provided to us without limiting your ability to view the remainder of the content on the web site.Finally, we never use or share with third parties the personally identifiable information provided to us online without your permission in ways other than as legally required or permitted. We may voluntarily cooperate with law enforcement agencies in investigating suspected illegal activity and may report to law enforcement any suspected illegal activity we become aware of.Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13.How to Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us toll-free Monday - Friday: 8 a.m. – 5 p.m. (Central Time) at (800) 627-4762 or provide your contact information in the Contact Us form located on this site. Please review this online privacy policy frequently as it may change at any time at Royal
Need Help
email us
call us
file a claim
In the MediaMedia Kit
Newsroom
Our Magazine
CareersWhere We Live
Form #:
P00182;
Rev. 6-2020
